Reach your hands out,
cut through the wind,
and forge ahead, drawing your own map as you go!
We can't even tell left from right
in this tempest-tossed era
Even the values we've honed
seem ready to crumble
Is the compass leading us true,
or is it leading us astray?
Nobody knows for sure!
Just breathe deep, close your eyes
and you'll find your soul guiding the way!
Reach your hands out,
cut through the wind,
away the darkness!
and kick aw
I'm doing this for myself,
and you're doing this for yourself too, right?
Forge ahead, painting the world in your own colors!
I am waiting for you...
Momonosuke!
I await your orders!
I have come here...
...to do battle at your side!
I spoke briefly with
Zunesha before this.
Incredible, Momonosuke-kun!
So you can converse with the elephant!
Just as Oden predicted!
You shall be the one to lead
the world unto a new Dawn!
Alas, we are missing
the most vital part to this...
By reading Father's journal, I understand
that I must live, no matter what.
And yet, he...
...tore out the
most important page himself!
Laugh Tale...
...the final island!
What did Roger, Father, and their crew
see there that made them laugh?
I do not understand
the import of what I must achieve!
Father was no prophet!
Were he here now, would he still say
"Open our borders" as he once did?!
I hardly consider myself wise!
If doing so were to put
the people of Wano in danger,
I would not want to open the borders!
Does this make me a coward,
Yamato?!
Carrot, head inside the dome!
We got our revenge!
But the battle's far from done!
Yes, sir!
Stay sharp...
Gotta stay sharp!
Who the heck knows when
this'll all come crashin' down...
This island gonna make it through?
I'm not lettin' fall!
ya
Got all beat up, as usual....
I'm pullin' ya up right now!
Hey! You're still breathin', right...
...Zoro?!
You didn't die on me, did ya?!
Zoro!
I won't let you die!
Stay with me!
Oh, crap... Crap! The castle looks like
it could collapse at any moment!
Where's the exit...?
Hamlet!
You can count on me,
my good man!
That's why I'm asking!
Make it your job!
Lives! Important!
Safe delivery!
Ow, hot, ow, hot, owhot!
Oww! Ouch!
'Tis hot, hot! 'Tis not!
Nay, 'tis... not hot! It's hot!
Even we ninja ought to enjoy
freedom in this day and age,
Fukurokuju!
Castle Interior, Third Floor,
Battle of the Connecting Passage...
The victor:
Raizo of the Mist!
Hey! Are you a samurai?!
Why aren't you running?!
You... are one of Luffy-dono's...
I must make haste!
You're in no state to do that!
Relax, now!
A shame...
I was fully prepared...
Hey, now!
Are you that eager to die?!
I would ask a favor!
Finger Pistol!
Shaving!
You must live...!
Kiku!
Damn!
Maha!
Damn you, Izo!
He planned to take us down
with him from the start...!
Damn it...
Why would some vestige of
Whitebeard's crew bother saving brats?!
Have to hurry and
find Nico Robin...!
Ring, ring, ring...
What now?! One damned
thing after another...
Clik.
Listen closely.
An Imperial Edict from
the Five Celestial Elders.
The Five Celestial Elders?
They declare...
"Eliminate Straw Hat Luffy at once"!
What are you telling me to do?!
Straw Hat is fighting
Kaido right now!
Are you telling me to
intervene in Kaido's fight?!
That's impossible!
They are well aware of the
impossible nature of the task.
It's a world-class battle,
which is why it presents a great risk.
Guess why that is.
The order is a necessary precaution.
A precaution against something
even the Five Celestial Elders are wary of...
Something we hardly know of
through rumors and guesswork.
Clik.
can't die without
having done anything!
What's so damned special...
...about that pirate crew?
Hihimaru...
Komachiyo...
Both of yas did great!
Boss!
Captain!
We beat Big Mom!
This is a huge deal!
Really huge!
You don't think Big Mom's
gonna come back after all that, do you...?
Mama!
Now hold on, Zeus!
Who's more important to you,
Big Mom or me?!
You, Nami!
You are!
Master! You must stay close to me!
Best keep on your toes
'til it's all over.
Right now, we're on...
...the most dangerous island
in the world, yessir!
Luffy... Are you still fighting?
Damn! Damn!
Damn it all!!!
How long is he going
to make me wait?!
Oh, Komurasaki!
Don't worry!
We'll make our way
out of here soon!
Fukurokuju!
That damned worthless ninja!
What could he possibly be doing?!
He couldn't have escaped
on his own, could he?!
Ninja have no freedom!
They are to live while
their lord does, and die alone!
Was that tremor earlier
Kanjuro's doing?
Hope that was the end of it...
H-Hey!
Komurasaki!
Why do you perform
at a time like this!!
That's enough!
Stop your performance!
This is a life-or-death situation,
and you're here, all pretentious and in a mask!
In fact, you've been
wearing it all along...
That mask...
Remove it at once!
Are you...
...truly...
...Komurasaki?
Are you a ghost?!
Did you notice?
Did you?!
Now they've gone and done it...
Those damn idiots...!
They got Linlin!
Jaggy and Traf did it?
Awesome!
You think we should ready up...
...for Kaido?
Nah, it's whatever.
If the one we see
coming down here is Kaido...
I don't have...
...the energy left to fight back...
You there, boy!
Got a mouth?
Hello?
Do you talk or not?
How old are ya?
Fifteen?!
So young!
First time joining Rocks' crew?
He's a good-for-nothin'!
Don't trust him.
If you got a problem,
you talk to me.
I'm Linlin!
I'm the woman who's
gonna rule the seas!
Nice t'meetcha!
Thinking about it now...
...we went way back, you and I...!
You damn hag!
I can't believe this happened...
...right as we vowed...
...to go take the One Piece!
Gear 4:
Snakeman!
DIANEMAN
Shaddap!
I'm in the middle of
reminiscin' here!
I... I can't move...!
I can't free myself!
You were so beside yourself...
So much so that
you failed to take notice.
Come now, Komurasaki!
Why are you just watching!!
Remove this rubble from me at once!
Damn it!
Why is it I can't transform?
So as to...
...prevent you from
transforming into a monster,
you were pierced with
a nail of Sea Stone...
by none other than I.
Why did...?!
What is this I'm hearing from you!!
I thought you loved me!
Love...? Absurd, coming from you.
I bear no love toward you.
Eh?!
By curious coincidence,
your favorite piece...
"Moon Princess"...
You have improved, Hiyori!
I've taken a liking to that song!
Really?! 'Tis called "Moon Princess!
I will improve even more!
What a beautiful song!
Play it at my funeral!
Now, Momo!
Do not make your sister cry!
'Twas your doing, Father!
Was it what I said earlier?
Ah, sorry. 'Twas in jest!
Really?!
I won't be dying!
'Tis the very piece...
...my father, Kozuki Oden, loved.
Every time I perform
"Moon Princess"...
I recall my father's face...
"Father"?!
How could I...
...ever...
...bear to smile...
...in front of you?!
Gum-Gum...
...Hydra!
I dun care 'bout
whatever goal you guys had!
Especially if it leaves
the guys here in this country...
...with no food to eat!
This's my last Gear 4!
The punchin' ain't stoppin'
'til I'm outta steam!
I've got no freakin' clue where
his punches are coming from!
I'm gonna...
...kick you outta Wano,
if it's the last thing I do!